Hello everyone welcome back to another edition of this just in. Ciao! Sorry interrupted you Marco. It's okay. I'm joined with the dynamic duo
Marco the Mutti's from Italian Pod. Ciao!
And Leonardo Guerrero from Spanish Pod. Hello. All right, so what happened to that nice
Marco the Mutti's introduction. Ciao! Yeah, that was banned. It was censored. No, it was censored.
Introduce. Yeah, I cannot do it anymore. I cannot do it anymore. It was banned. Yeah, it was banned.
Yeah, it was vetoed. Vetoed. By jealous people who wanted it all for themselves. What's next?
I don't know. I don't know. They're gonna kick me out of the show or what?
Look I think I don't know if if the situation keeps on going on like this with the you know censoring me
I'm gonna just you know go out where and out. We're not that lucky. Somewhere.
Why are we here? Hyde Park in the speaker's corner. We're here as always to talk about the lessons and
Marco if you if you actually had the chance to go to Hyde Park in London that you know the speaker's corner, right?
What would you say?
You're a little stall you go there you go up there and you can say whatever you feel like to
Anybody. Yeah, maybe I would just be doing this just in there. Just yelling
I love it with me and Leo. With you and yeah. By my side.
That could be cool. That could be cool. Let's ask our bosses for a budget.
Yeah, but you have to shout more than the guy who's directly from London.
Yeah, but next to you there's a guy that's saying like the Lord will save you.
It's gonna be very loud. No, no, we'll have a loudspeakers or something. We'll take the microphones. Nice. Yeah.
So you were saying something so I interrupted you again. Well, it's okay because we have some great lessons coming up this week.
Again? Again. You always say that. Well, because they're always cool. And you know what we're approaching lesson number 100 very soon. Wow, happy birthday.
Way. You know in Italian part we just reached 200 the other day. Really? Yeah. Wow. How does it feel?
I feel very old. How many hours of voice do you think you've recorded so far? I think 30 light years.
That measured distance.
It's like very far.
Your voice has traveled very far. And Spanish but it's getting to 400. Wow. So you're the baby.
Yeah, we're the younglings here. I remember when we had our first 100 party. Yeah.
How many? Everybody was naked drunk. Incredible. Yeah. Don't do that. English but you don't do that. That's dangerous.
How many lessons on
Chef Tabasco do you have? Cooking with Tabasco? I think we're about. Chef. It's not chef Marcus. Chef. Chef. Chef.
Cooking with Tabasco, please. Okay. How many?
15. 15? Yeah. Wow. If you guys ever want to check out some Mexican recipes, be sure to go to Spanishpot.com
That's where Leo teaches you how to cook delicious
Mexican food. It's actually pretty good. It's pretty good. I watched it. I tried it at home and
No, you didn't. It was exactly the same. I felt like I was in Mexico City. You can't even cook an instant noodle soup.
I felt like I was in Mexico City. I was like, whoo. Hey Marco, do you really know how to cook? With the flu and everything.
I know the basics. Like what can you make? You can do like cereal with milk. No, I can do pasta as a different kind of pasta.
You can do pasta.
Shut the front door.
You know, there was this post recently that they said that some of the most useless things in the world are the different types of Italian pasta.
Why do you have so many little bow ties? Who said that? It must be some an engineer with all due respect to the category.
But there was somebody who was like a physicist maybe. Yeah, I think so.
Why do you have so many different types of pasta? Okay, I'm gonna answer your question with another question. Okay. Why not?
There's a funny, there's a fun.
Little ones, long ones. It's confusing. What is there to be confused? Well, you don't know which one to choose sometimes.
Yeah, it's like. And sometimes you'll cook.
And then sometimes you'll have Italian friends over for dinner and you'll be like, hey, I cooked some pasta.
And they're like, I can't believe you use that sauce with this noodle.
Yeah, why did you do ravioli with this? With Tabasco. Yeah. Why? Why?
Why not? Why not?
No, it doesn't work both ways. All right.
So anyways, if you guys want to go and get some groceries or some money to buy these ingredients.
Don't put ketchup on pizza. Cooking. You can listen to Monday's lesson going to the ATM. Put Tabasco on pizza.
Don't put Tabasco on pizza. So we're going to the ATM on Monday.
Are we going? Did we get paid? Yeah, we did. We're going with no card though. With no card.
We're going to go. Yeah. And hope that the ATM will go.
You know, when you're a child and you go to the arcade, to the video games, you have no coins or anything.
So you fake like you play. Oh, yes. Yeah. Have you done that?
I wasn't that lame when I was a kid. Have you done that at an ATM?
I usually do that at an ATM too. I do that song with your mouth.
That's what you should do an ATM. You should go into your car, take out money.
Go like I won. Oh, my God. Look at all this money I'm getting.
That's what I do when I get the change at the ticket machine at the subway.
So what's the next lesson? Next lesson, we're going on Wednesday to the pharmacy.
Nice. We're going all over. So we're going to buy shampoo and condoms and that toothbrush.
Well, now that you mention it, we are going to be buying some of these. What are they called?
What are they called? Prophylactics. Prophylactics. What?
I think that's the technical name for the rubber.
Durex. Durex is a rubber assistance of contraception.
Rubber is a safe sex device. Have you seen those ones with stripes?
Okay, enough. We don't hang out in the same neighborhood as they are.
We don't want to go into those details. Those shirts with stripes.
Where do you go to buy them? In the pharmacy? No, Walmart.
Walmart. How many do you buy? Walmart has a pharmacy.
Really? Yeah. No, they don't. Yeah, it's Walmart pharmacy.
Do you usually feel awkward or a bit embarrassed when you buy them?
Like you try to avoid eye contact with the shop assistant?
I used to. I used to buy a lot of stuff at the beginning.
Every time I need to buy, like, prophylactics, I had to buy like,
oh, shampoo, toothbrush, and that cream over there.
Yeah, that health stuff. Prophylactics.
30 euros. What? What?
30 euros with a little box of condoms?
All right, so we're going to not only be getting condoms,
we're also going to be getting medicine.
Yeah, that's why, because you want to mess with the fact that you want to buy condoms.
Well, yeah, sometimes. It's just convenient.
And on Friday, we're going to be looking at Leo's favorite sport, baseball.
Yes! He was cricket. I thought it was chess.
Chess? Is that a sport? Well, yeah.
It's not a sport. It's a board game. It depends how fast you play.
What happens to your hair, Marco? If you go like,
Marco has some weird hairstyle now.
You realize that this is an audio podcast.
They can't see you.
Oh, we're not having the video camera this time.
I think it's broken. Yeah, it's okay.
So anyways, those are the three lessons coming out next week.
Baseball, pharmacy, and going to the ATM.
So, baseball is the American national pastime,
so we're going to be learning about that vocabulary.
What is a strike? What is an inning?
I'm going to explain the rules, because I don't understand.
No, we don't have enough time to explain the rules.
It's pretty complicated. But it is complicated, yeah.
Especially for dumb Italians like you.
Totally, because I get a game where all the players are...
Half the players are running in a direction.
Half of the other players are running in the opposite direction,
like soccer. But in baseball,
each one of those guys do something different.
The guy that takes the ball, the guy has the bat,
and they have different accessories.
One has the bat, one has a funny glove,
one is running in circles.
He's like, what is this, the circus?
You know what's great about it?
That it's relaxing, you know, while the team is there,
they're waiting to bat, so they're just sitting there talking,
chewing gum, reading books, listening to music.
I think this news and video show is very relaxing,
compared to the other ones we do.
Yeah, something's going on.
Did you guys... Did you guys...
What?
No, nothing. It's all right.
What? You're crazy.
You're crazy as a knife.
I'm crazy as a knife? How is a knife crazy?
I don't know, I'm already from French,
but the other day came in and said like,
oh, yes, back, I'm fresh as a knife.
Fresh as a knife.
Fresh as a knife, and I thought it was quite funny.
So you wanted to use it for crazy?
I'm using it for everything, it works just fine.
Wow, yeah, very good.
All right, so...
All right, and now...
The user of the week.
Our user of the week is kind of anonymous.
His name is User 2048.
2048.
Yeah, so I wonder what 2048 means.
No, I guess that's a sign automatically by a computer
for those people who don't choose a username.
Really?
Just spoil the magic.
Yeah, you spoil the magic.
I'm sorry.
Why do you work in CRM?
See, you shouldn't know these things.
You spoil it for us.
Okay, so...
All right, so user...
So he's lazy, basically, because he was...
Are you saying that he was lazy
and he didn't choose a name?
No, he wasn't very creative.
No!
He just wanted to protect his name.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
He doesn't trust you.
User 2048 is actually...
I think he's a native English speaker,
because he lives in the States.
Why don't he tell us?
Why didn't he tell us?
Tell us.
Explain it.
We are breaking our heads here,
trying to figure out why this is.
Our ears are open.
All right, so he helps out a lot in the community.
He corrects some of the sentences
that people post in the comments section, so...
Oh, he's a really good Samaritan.
He's a really good help.
Nice.
He's a native...
So basically stealing your job, Marc.
He should pay him.
No, no, no.
He helps out.
With your salary.
We'll send him a Marco action figure.
By the way, how are we at Marco action figures?
Fresh as a knife!
Spicy!
That would be nice.
All right, so that's all for today.
A relaxed, nice way to start off May.
Yeah.
Why didn't we have a guest this time?
Well, apparently we...
Nobody wants to be our guest anymore.
Nobody wants to be a guest anymore.
They're afraid of us.
Some people complain that we treated Jordan very badly.
Yeah.
I think it's necessary to point out that Jordan is evil.
But he's an intern.
Yeah, but he's not paid.
You know we have another intern, Bo.
Maybe we'll have him.
Oh, we should have him.
We should have Bo on.
All right, that's all for today.
Have fun, guys.
Listen to our dialogues and to our lessons next week.
And if you have time, be sure to go to Italian Pod and Spanish Pod as well.
Dot-com, at the end.
We're both.
Yeah.
Okay, see you guys there.
Ciao.
Bye.
EnglishPod.com.